Xenon：Damnit! Can't open it.
Xenon：제길! 열리지 않아!
Xenon：Hey! Is anyone there!?
Xenon：이봐! 안에 누구 없어!?
Xenon：The backup lighting is still on... Only the main power source is dead, is it?
Xenon：비상등에 불은 들어와있는데...메인 전원만 망가진 건가...?
Cherry：... Ugh...
Cherry：...윽....
Xenon：Sherry!? Are you awake?
Xenon：Sherry!? 깨어났어!?
Xenon：So this means that the entire life support system has stopped functioning...?
Xenon：생명 유지 시스템도 모두 나가버린 건가...?
Cherry：Haa... I feel... awful...
Cherry：하아... 더 이상은...
Xenon：Hang in there. I'll call someone here right away!
Xenon：조금만 버텨! 당장 사람을 불러올게!
Xenon：My device is also outside, or else I would've had a chance to hack this door open...
Xenon：제길! 내 장비들만이라도 이곳에 있었다면 문 여는 일 따윈...
Xenon：What exactly is going on?
Xenon：대체 무슨 일이 벌어진 거지?
Cherry：Haah...
Cherry：하아...
Xenon：Sherry, are you alright?
Xenon：Sherry! 괜찮아!?
Cherry：... Can you come closer? I want you... by my side.
Cherry：....내... 내 옆으로 와볼래...?
Xenon：... Yeah.
Xenon：...응.
Cherry：Feels like... I had a really weird dream...
Cherry：뭔가... 이상한 꿈을 꾼 것 같아...
Cherry：... I was standing on a pitch-black water surface, constantly looking for a flower... A blue... illuminating flower.
Cherry：...내가... 새까만 물 위에서 꽃을 찾고 있었어... 파란색... 빛이 나는 꽃을...
Cherry：Whenever I was about to touch it, it disappeared. This repeated itself, again and again...
Cherry：내가 그 꽃을 만지려고 할 때마다 자꾸 사라졌어... 끊임없이 그 행동을 반복하는데....
Cherry：For some reason, I feel... that it's something very important. If I don't find it... I will lose everything...
Cherry：엄청... 중요한 것이라고 생각했던 것 같아... 그걸 찾지 못하면.... 모든 걸 잃게 될 것만 같은 기분이 들었어...
Cherry：If I can return to the dream, maybe I'll be able to find it this time.
Cherry：만약에 다시 꿈속으로 들어가면... 아마 찾아낼 수 있을지도 몰라...
Xenon：It's just a dream.
Xenon：그냥 꿈일 뿐이야.
Xenon：Don't fall asleep. The system should be restored very soon. Nora would never leave a situation like this unaddressed.
Xenon：우선 잠들지 말고 있어. 시스템이 금방 복구될 거야. Nora가 이대로 가만히 내버려 두진 않을 거야.
Cherry：... Yeah.
Cherry：응....
Cherry：I kind of understand what you meant by "let go of the past" now...
Cherry：예전에 네가... 「내려놓아라」라고 말했던 의미를 조금 알 것 같아...
Cherry：Perhaps the thing I want to pursue never existed in the first place...
Cherry：아마 내가 찾고 싶었던 것은 사실 존재한 적이 없던 것일지도...
Cherry：But... you're here.
Cherry：그래도... 네가 여기에 있으니까...
Xenon：... Yes, I'm here.
Xenon：....응... 네 말대로 지금 이렇게 니 옆에 있어....
Cherry：Hey, sing "Still" for me...
Cherry：《Still》... 불러줘....
Xenon：......
Xenon：.......
Cherry：Come on... it's not like there's anybody else here...
Cherry：불러줘... 여기 우리 말고 아무도 없잖아...
Xenon：... Okay.
Xenon：......알았어.
Xenon：You don't have to cover yourself
Xenon：You don't have to cover yourself
Xenon：When no one can be trust
Xenon：When no one can be trust
Xenon：I'm still here standing beside you
Xenon：I'm still here standing beside you
Xenon：But they torn us apart
Xenon：But they torn us apart
Xenon：And I still keep you, inside my broken heart.
Xenon：And I still keep you, inside my broken heart.
Cherry：...... Haha......
Cherry：……하하……
Cherry：... Your singing...
Cherry：……진짜……
Cherry：sucks......
Cherry：더럽게 못 부른다니까……